bamsec.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy – BamSEC

### Introduction

BamSEC ("us", "we", "our") operates the bamsec.com website (the "Site"). This page describes how we protect your personal data that we process and control ("your personal data", "your data", "your information") and your personal data rights. We are committed to the privacy of your information when you use BamSEC.

### Information BamSEC Collects and How We Use It

###### a. Information you volunteer

When you register to use BamSEC we ask for information such as your name, email address, and credit card information. BamSEC uses collected registration information for the following general purposes such as: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, and contact. We may also collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail.

###### b. Information we collect from your usage

Our Site use cookies to work properly. Our cookies store information such as your usage of our Site and your Internet browser and device data for a period of time. For more information about our usage of cookies, please see the Cookies section below.

We also collect information on user activity on our Site such as which pages are visited, and we may use third party analytics providers such as Google Analytics to collect user activity information (Google's privacy policy can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy)). We also use Stripe and the services it provides in order to process payments (Stripe's privacy policy can be found [here](https://stripe.com/us/privacy)).

All information we collect is used strictly to improve the content of our Site and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except when we have your express permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if BamSEC is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, BamSEC will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We follow industry best practices in securing access to the data, encrypting connections, and protecting your information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We may use both session cookies and permanent cookies. You are required to re-login to BamSEC account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents. Your web browser may allow you to modify your cookie preferences. Please note that cookies are required to use the BamSEC service.

### Why BamSEC Needs Your Information

We need to collect your basic personal information (such as name, email address, and credit card information) in order provide you with our service and receive customer feedback.

### Data Storage

BamSEC uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run BamSEC. We follow industry best practices in securing access to all data. Although BamSEC owns the code, databases, and all rights to the BamSEC application, you retain all rights to your data.

### Data Transfers

BamSEC is based in the United States, so your information may be collected and processed in the United States. United States privacy, data protection, and data storage laws may be different from those in your country. BamSEC is committed to protecting your data and will take measures to ensure that data transfers meet the requirements of applicable laws.

### Your Rights

Depending on your location and subject to applicable law, here are a few of the rights that you may have as an individual to the use, collection, and storage of your data by BamSEC:

  * You have the right to request and obtain a copy of your personal data.
  * You have the right to correct any incomplete or inaccurate personal data
  * You have the right to have your personal data erased
  * You have the right to request that BamSEC stop processing your data
  * You have the right to request that BamSEC only processes your data in limited circumstances
  * You have the right to request a copy of your personal data that BamSEC has collected, or request BamSEC to transfer that data to another data controller.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us as described in the below Contact section.

### Contact

Please email us at [contact@bamsec.com](mailto:contact@bamsec.com?subject=BamSEC) should you have any questions about this Privacy Policy.
